翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
正如大家所知
So, as you guys know,
使用AI工具翻译，如有不准确的地方请在弹幕或评论区指正，谢谢！
美国政府最近公布了爱泼斯坦的文件
the government of the United States released the Epstein files recently.
其中大部分内容都被涂改得面目全非
Most of them were redacted into oblivion,
甚至完全空白
if not entirely blank.
但有一份爱泼斯坦的文件特别引起了我的注意
But there is one Epstein file specifically that caught my eye.
那是一张东芝笔记本电脑底部的照片
It's a picture of the underside of a Toshiba laptop.
幸运的是 与其他所有不重要的东西不同
Luckily, unlike all the other unimportant stuff,
这份文件完全没有被涂改 上面有一个勉强能辨认的Windows 7产品密钥
this file is entirely unredacted and there is a Windows 7 product key barely discernible.
那么 我们能用爱泼斯坦的笔记本电脑激活Windows吗？
So, can we activate Windows using Epstein's laptop?
无论是Windows 10还是Windows 11 都无法再直接用Windows 7的密钥激活了
Neither Windows 10 nor Windows 11 can be directly activated with the Windows 7 key anymore.
微软已经禁用了这个功能
Microsoft disabled that capability.
但是 我们能使用那个密钥激活Windows 7吗？
However, can we activate Windows 7 with that key?
让我们来一探究竟
Let's find out.
为此 我们需要启动一个Windows 7虚拟机
For that purpose, we will need to spin up a Windows 7 VM.
这是一个Windows 7家庭高级版的官方证书类型产品密钥
This is a certificate of authority type of product key for Windows 7 Home Premium.
所以 为了确保无误 我会获取Windows 7家庭高级版的ISO镜像
So, to be sure, I'll get the Windows 7 Home Premium ISO.
而且我必须提一下
And I just have to mention,
这台笔记本电脑在2010年代初其实相当不错
this laptop isn't bad at all for the beginning of 2010s.
它是一台东芝Satellite L635
It's a Toshiba Satellite L635.
他能拥有这样的设备真是令人惊讶
Crazy the fact he got to own such a device.
那时候他不是在监狱里吗？
Wasn't he in prison by that point?
不过无论如何 让我们在虚拟机上安装Windows 7家庭高级版
But anyways, let's install Windows 7 Home Premium on a virtual machine.
这是我人生中第一次
This is the first time,
也可能是最后一次
and potentially the last time in my lifetime,
在一台机器上安装Windows家庭高级版
I'm actually installing Windows Home Premium on a machine.
因为它功能太少了
Because it just lacks features.
我记得好像没有组策略编辑器之类的
I think there's no GPEdit or something.
凭记忆来说
Off the top of my head,
可能也没有远程桌面功能
maybe there is no RDP either.
安装家庭高级版实在没什么意义
It just makes no sense to install Home Premium.
直接装旗舰版不就好了
Just get Ultimate.
不过我怀疑爱泼斯坦根本不会去折腾他Windows 7笔记本上的组策略
But I doubt Epstein would care to tweak the group policy on his Windows 7 laptop,
对吧？
right?
他连组策略是什么都不知道
He wouldn't even know what a group policy is.
这该死的PDF文件
Stupid-ass pdf file.
好吧 这时候Windows 7已经装好了
Okay, by that point Windows 7 was installed,
我在产品密钥上费了点劲
and I struggled a bit with the product key.
模糊的拍摄画质让密钥边缘都快看不清了
It's like on the edge of being redacted by the poor camera quality.
但试了几次之后
But after a couple attempts,
我还是成功输入了
I got it.
你觉得呢
And what do you think,
这会是有效的Windows 7密钥吗？
it's a valid Windows 7 key?
太好了！
Yippee!
不过拿到有效密钥
Having a valid key on our hands,
只是万里长征第一步
though, is only part of the ordeal.
我们需要在微软后端服务器激活它密钥才能被判定为有效正版
We need to activate it on the Microsoft backend servers for the key to count as valid and genuine.
这是个格式正确的密钥
It's a key with a valid format,
但能否在后端成功激活系统还有待验证
and we're yet to find out if it's actually going to activate our install on the backend.
现在显示着产品ID和激活通知
So here is the product ID and the activation notification.
开始激活吧
Let's run it.
我们立刻遇到了错误
We're immediately faced with an error.
您输入的Windows 7家庭高级版产品密钥无法用于激活
The Windows 7 Home Premium product key you typed is invalid for activation.
不过我在往期视频里解释过 这并非绝境
However, I've already explained in the past videos it's not a dead end.
微软的激活机制相当复杂
The Microsoft activation mechanism is quite complex.
这个密钥之所以被判定无效 是因为Windows试图通过内网自动激活
The reason this key is considered invalid is because Windows tries to activate it automatically via the intranet,
而失败的原因在于每个COA密钥仅有一次通过内网直接激活的机会
and it fails because there is only one chance per COA key for direct intranet activation.
COA（Certificate of Authenticity）密钥，也就是那个笔记本下面的密钥贴纸
不过通过电话激活Windows 还能获得多次额外的机会
However, you can have multiple extra chances activating Windows with a phone.
在密钥被列入黑名单之前可以进行5到10次电话激活 之后便无法再使用该密钥激活系统
5 to 10 times you can do that before the key gets blacklisted and you can't activate the install with it anymore.
我们无法享受内网直接激活的原因是杰弗里·爱泼斯坦本人
Basically, the reason we can't enjoy direct intranet activation is because Jeffrey Epstein himself used that activation
过去曾用这个密钥激活过他的Windows系统
key in the past to activate his Windows install.
但凭借我们对Windows激活机制的了解 我们依然可以使用这个密钥
But thanks to our knowledge of the Windows activation mechanism we can use that key regardless.
如果你动作够快 你或许也能在爱泼斯坦密钥被列入黑名单前使用它
If you're fast enough,you can probably use the Epstein key as well before it gets blacklisted
因为尝试电话激活的人实在太多了
because too many people tried to activate that key via phone.
看来这意味着我又得打国际长途了
So surely that means I have to call overseas again.
不 现在已经不是这样了
Nope, that's not a thing anymore.
微软已于2025年12月20日关闭电话激活中心
Microsoft has retired the call activation centers on December 20th of 2025.
我制作的所有关于电话激活的视频都已成历史
All the videos I've made about phone activation are now history.
确实有种超现实的感觉
That feels kind of surreal.
无论如何 我们现在都得使用在线激活门户了
Either way, we have to use the online activation portal now.
电话激活的理念依然未变
The idea of phone activation remains the same,
只是现在能为微软节省更多成本
it just costs Microsoft less money now.
但如今没有内网连接就无法激活微软产品
And you can't activate Microsoft products without an intranet connection anymore,
这确实令人遗憾
which sucks.
幸运的是 这次激活成功了
Luckily, it was a success.
不过有趣的是 爱泼斯坦密钥被识别为Microsoft Office 2010的密钥
However, the Epstein key was labeled as a key for Microsoft Office 2010,
这确实很有意思
which is really funny,
但我仍想制作视频解释这种现象的成因
but I still want to make a video explaining why that happens.
现在让我们将确认ID填入对应框格 完成这次激活
Let's input the confirmation ID into the boxes and get this puppy activated.
太棒了！
Nice!
激活已成功完成
The activation was successful.
这无疑证实了爱泼斯坦的笔记本电脑
So this definitely proves the Epstein's laptop has been set up,
曾被激活并至少使用过一次
activated and used at least once.
这最终意味着什么？
What does it ultimately mean?
我尚不明确 但实验数据已给出证明
I don't know, but that's been experimentally proven just now.
Purple Place的冲击力从未如此强烈
Purple Place has never hit that hard.
那么 本次内容就到这里
And yeah, I think that's it for now.
感谢您的观看
Thanks for watching.
祝您拥有美好的一天
I hope you have a great day.
原标题：Activating Windows using the most controversial laptop 原作者：Enderman
原视频上传日期：2026年1月11日
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
字幕制作不易，喜欢的话支持一下我吧！
在 Youtube 上关注